{
    "id": "1d002969ed854b5b9804174c6a31a7c8",
    "title": "Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She congratulated …………………………..",
            "description": "When the subject and the object refer to the same person, use the reflexive pronoun.",
            "answers": [
                "herself",
                "her",
                "hers"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "915170c42e334ab084bf91b41cddedf7"
        },
        {
            "question": "You are worse than …………………………….",
            "description": "Object pronouns are considered more appropriate after as and than.",
            "answers": [
                "himself",
                "he",
                "him"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "48b64b104e6e42269bb4612057ee2d80"
        },
        {
            "question": "He stabbed ………………………….. with a knife.",
            "description": "When the subject and the object refer to the same person, use the reflexive pronoun. ",
            "answers": [
                "him",
                "himself",
                "his"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6b31f7784fd04609b3f7b06008411228"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘Whose car is this?’ ‘It is …………………………..’",
            "description": "It is hers means the same as it is her car. ",
            "answers": [
                "her",
                "hers",
                "herself"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "473880b6e1ee40029bf2e99fd13ecec0"
        },
        {
            "question": "He lives on ………………………….. own.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "his",
                "himself",
                "him"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "14255d3c1a3842d6b2aeb7bbba5cdcc5"
        },
        {
            "question": "I did it …………………………… as there was no one to help me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "myself",
                "myselves",
                "me"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "66d6fc1b4ff94d08a3e9c87610f0ccf3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Please eat more vegetables and do …………………………. a favor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "you",
                "yourself",
                "yours"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "09ade4f31ece4f4bb5d9fc679080c70d"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is your fault, not ………………………….",
            "description": "Not mine means the same as not my fault. ",
            "answers": [
                "me",
                "mine",
                "myself"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "07eb945e34d74269bc492f9866dab98b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I showed her my ID proof, but she couldn’t show me ………………………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "her",
                "hers",
                "herself"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a33baefc0ed94b9190f4ab8f773ece34"
        },
        {
            "question": "That cat of ………………………….. has drank my milk.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "your",
                "yours",
                "yourself"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7d8df46941b847d7bddac8b58baeaa98"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………………….. spoke to the Minister.",
            "description": "For emphasis, use the emphatic pronoun.",
            "answers": [
                "myself",
                "me",
                "myselves"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4c2af0d4c64f4fc6926d4878c1f1f8d1"
        },
        {
            "question": "This cat is …………………………..",
            "description": "That cat is theirs means the same as that is their cat. ",
            "answers": [
                "their",
                "theirs",
                "them"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "59c0c261926b448d832e174b01f62891"
        }
    ]
}